[news anchor on radio]
The news never ends.
This is 1080 GCR.
You get all the news you
need, all day long.
Good morning.
It's 42 degrees at 10:30 on this
Thursday, October 15th.
I'm Stan L.
Brooks, and here's what's happening.
It's day 18
of the garbage strike,
with 10,000 tons of garbage
piling up every day.
Even the nicest sections
of the city
are looking like slums.
Health Commissioner
Edward O'Rourke is
declaring a city-wide
state of emergency
for the first time in decades.
[O'Rourke] There's no need
to wait until somebody dies
or comes down
with typhoid fever.
It's already
a serious situation.
[news anchor] It's
something that affects
almost everyone
in the city,
no matter who they are
or where they live.
[man 1] You can't go
down no one avenue
without seeing nothing
but garbage and rats.
[man 2] It's starting to
affect my business
when customers
can't get in here
because of
the garbage situation.
[woman 1] I'm not out
that long to smell it,
but I think to look at
it, it's terrible.
[man 3] It don't
affect me except
for the very bad
smell here.
It's horrific.
[woman 2] It's a mess.
I've been in this country
for 50 years,
and I've never seen
anything like it.
What is this world
coming to?
[man 4] Put 'em
in a room,
let 'em sit there and talk
until they get it over with.
24 hours, 48 hours,
how long it takes.
[man 5] The idea of the
National Guard moving in
and cleaning up
is a good idea.
[news anchor] In other news,
the building industry
and landlords today
expressed concern
over the latest
increase in
heating oil prices.
Renters in the metro area
are certain to
feel the pinch...
[grunts sadly]
[upbeat music
playing on piano]
[people chattering
and yelling]
[car horns honking]
[boy 1] Yo, what's up
with your shoes, bro?
[boy 2] Nice outfit, pal.
[boy 1] If you're gonna be a
clown, at least you could be
a good one.
You know that, right?
- [Arthur] Hey! Hey!
- [boy 3] Grab it!
[boy 4] Go, go, go!
[Arthur] Hey!
[boy 2] He's coming!
Come on, clown, let's go!
We've got the sign.
- [boy 2] Look at him running.
- [boy 1] Let's go!
Stop them!
[boy 1] Go, go, go, go!
Watch the car, watch the car!
- [horns honking]
- [laughs mockingly]
[boy 1] Where's
your sign, clown?
- [driver] Hey!
- [yelps]
[horns honking]
[panting]
[boy 1] Go, clown!
Come on!
Stop them!
[boys shouting]
Go! Come on!
[Arthur] Stop them!
Come on, run!
Hey!
You fucking...
[continues panting]
- [groans]
- [boy 2] Oh, shit! Good hit.
[boy 1] Come on!
Beat his ass up.
Come on! This guy's weak.
He can't do nothing.
Harder! Harder!
Beat him up.
Take his stuff.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on. Let's go!
[breathing heavily]
[groans]
[labored breathing]
[strained laughing]
[clears throat]
[continues laughing]
Ha!
[chuckling]
[laughing]
[wheezes]
[grunts]
[laughing]
[wheezes]
[clears throat]
[laughing tearfully]
[Arthur chuckles]
[Arthur sniffles]
Is it just me,
or is it getting
crazier out there?
- It is certainly tense.
- Hmm.
People are upset.
They're struggling.
Looking for work.
These are tough times.
[exhales]
How about you?
Have you been keeping
up with your journal?
Yes, ma'am.
Great.
Did you bring it
with you?
Arthur.
Last time,
I asked you to bring your journal
with you
for these appointments.
Can I see it?
I've been using it as a journal,
but also
as a joke diary.
Funny thoughts
or observations.
I think
I told you
I'm pursuing a career
in stand-up comedy.
No, you didn't.
I think I did.
"I just hope my death makes
more sense than my life."
[laughs]
How does it feel to
have to come here?
Does it help to have
someone to talk to?
I think
I felt better
when I was locked
up in the hospital.
And have you
thought more about
why you were
locked up?
[head thudding]
Who knows?
I was wondering if you
could ask the doctor
to increase
my medication.
Arthur, you're on
seven different medications.
Surely,
they must be doing something.
I just don't want to
feel so bad anymore.
[gasps]
[laughing]
Would you please
stop bothering my kid?
I wasn't bothering him.
I was...
Just stop.
[Arthur laughing]
What?
You think that's funny?
[continues laughing]
[gagging]
I'm sorry. I have a...
[laughing]
I'm sorry.
[continues laughing]
[woman exhales]
[Arthur continues laughing]
[music playing]
[exhales]
[Penny] Happy,
did you check the mail
before you came up?
Yeah, Mom.
Nothing.
[news anchor 1 on TV]
And finally, tonight,
just when you thought
it couldn't get any worse...
...authorities are saying
the city is under siege
by scores of rats.
And not just any rats,
but super rats,
who are hard to kill.
He must not be
getting my letters.
Yeah.
It's Thomas Wayne,
Mom.
He's a busy man.
Please. I worked for
that family for years.
The least he could do
is write back.
Here. Don't get all worked up.
Eat.
You need to eat.
Look how skinny you are.
[clears throat]
[news anchor 1] Both victims
were taken to Gotham General.
[news anchor 2]
Sounds like
the city needs to
find the Pied Piper.
He'll make a great mayor.
Everybody says so.
Oh, yeah. Everybody who?
Who do you talk to?
Well, everybody
on the news.
He's the only one who
could save the city.
He owes it to us.
- [theme music playing]
- Come sit. It's starting.
Yay, Murray.
[announcer on TV] From NCB
Studios in Gotham City,
it's Live with
Murray Franklin!
Tonight, Murray welcomes
Sandra Winger...
Oh, Sandra Winger's on.
...and the piano stylings
of Yeldon and Chantel.
Joining Murray,
as always,
Ellis Drane
and his jazz orchestra.
And now,
without further ado,
Murray Franklin.
- [upbeat jazz music playing]
- [audience cheering]
- [music ends]
- [audience cheering loudly]
- Thank you.
- [Arthur cheering]
Thank you.
We got a great-looking
audience tonight.
Yeah!
Wow. Thank you.
Thank you.
So, everybody's heard
about the super rats that
- are in Gotham now, right?
- [audience] Yeah.
Well, today,
the mayor said he has a solution.
You ready for this?
Super cats.
[all laughing]
But in all seriousness,
I mean, these rats are...
[Arthur] I love you,
Murray!
[audience chuckling]
I love you, too.
[all laughing]
Hey, Bobby,
would you put the lights on?
Who is that?
Was that you?
You wanna stand up, please?
Stand up for me.
Go ahead.
What's your name?
Hi, Murray. Arthur.
- Arthur?
- My name's Arthur.
Oh, okay. Well,
there's something special about you,
Arthur, I could tell.
Where are you from?
I live right here
in the city
- with my [stammers] mother.
- [audience laughing]
[Murray] Okay, hold on. Hold on.
There's nothing funny
about that.
I lived with my mother before I made it.
Just me and her.
I'm that kid whose father went
out for a pack of cigarettes,
and he never
came back.
[audience] Aww.
[Arthur] I know
what that's like, Murray.
I've been the man of the house
for as long as I can remember.
I take good care
of my mother.
All that sacrifice,
she must love you very much.
She does.
She always tells me to smile
and put on a happy face.
She says I was put here to
spread joy and laughter.
[audience] Aww.
Wow.
I like that. I like that a lot.
Come on down.
Come on.
For that, you gotta come down.
- [audience cheering]
- Come on! Come on.
[upbeat jazz music playing]
Come on.
[audience cheering loudly]
Okay, we got a big show tonight.
Stay tuned.
We'll be right back.
That was great, Arthur.
Thank you.
I mean, I loved hearing
what you had to say.
It made my day.
Thanks, Murray.
You see all this,
the lights, the show,
the audience,
all that stuff?
I'd give it all up
in a heartbeat
to have a kid
like you.
[stretching shoe]
- [indistinct chattering]
- [music playing on radio]
[sighs]
- [Randall] What's up, ladies?
- Hey, Randall. What's up?
Another day
in chuckle town.
[man] Yup.
You okay?
I heard about
the beatdown you took.
Fucking savages.
It was just a bunch of kids.
I should have left it alone.
No.
They'll take everything
from you if you do that.
All the crazy shit
out there.
- They're animals.
- [chuckles]
You know what?
Here.
What is it?
Take it.
It's for you.
[chuckling]
[Randall] You gotta
protect yourself out there.
Otherwise,
you're gonna get fucked.
Randall,
I'm not supposed to
have a gun.
Don't sweat it, Art.
No one
has to know.
And you can pay me
back some other time.
You know
you're my boy.
[laughing]
[Gary] Arthur,
Hoyt wants to
see you in his office.
Hey, Gary.
You know what I've always wondered?
No idea.
Do you people call it
miniature golf
or is it just golf
to you?
[Randall and Arthur
laughing]
[man] Punch him in the
dick, Gary.
[laughing]
Hello, Hoyt.
Gary said you wanted to see me.
How's the comedy career?
Are you a famous stand-up yet?
Not quite.
Just been working
on my material.
No, don't sit.
This'll be quick.
Look,
I like you, Arthur.
You know,
a lot of the guys,
they think you're a freak,
but I like you.
I don't even know
why I like you.
But I got
another complaint.
It's starting to piss me off.
Kenny's Music.
The guy said
you disappeared.
Never even
returned his sign.
Because I got jumped.
Didn't you hear?
For a sign?
That's bullshit.
It doesn't even make sense.
Just get him
his sign back.
He's going out of business,
for God's sake, Arthur.
Why would
I keep his sign?
How the fuck do I know?
Why does anybody do anything?
If you don't
return the sign,
I gotta take it
out of your paycheck.
Are we clear?
Listen,
I'm trying to help you.
Okay? And I'll tell you
something else.
The other guys,
they don't feel comfortable
around you, Arthur,
because people
think you're weird.
Okay? And I can't
have that around me.
[Hoyt continues indistinctly]
[grunting]
[elevator bell dings]
[jabbing buttons]
[Sophie] Wait,
wait, wait.
Wait.
Thank you.
[GiGi giggles]
This building is so
awful, isn't it?
awful, right, Mommy?
Yes, we can
hear you, GiGi.
It's so awful,
Mommy.
[imitates gunshot]
Right, Mommy?
[elevator bell dings]
- Good night.
- [GiGi] This building's
- so awful, isn't it?
- Mmm-hmm.
- [baby crying]
- [man shouting]
Hey.
[imitates gunshot]
Come on.
[upbeat music playing]
[door closes]
- [Arthur] Look up.
- [Penny] Mmm.
Maybe the mailman's
throwing them away.
Mom, why are these letters
so important to you?
What do you think
he's gonna do?
He's gonna help us.
But you worked for him,
what, 30 years ago?
Why would
he help us?
Because Thomas Wayne
is a good man.
If he knew
how we were living,
if he saw this place,
it would make him sick.
I can't explain it to
you any better than that.
I don't want you worrying
about money, Mom.
Or me.
Everybody's telling me
that my stand-up's
ready for the big clubs.
But, Happy, what makes you
think you could do that?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
Don't you have to be
funny to be a comedian?
[men on TV singing]
[Arthur imitates gunshot]
Hey, what's your name?
Arthur.
Hey, Arthur,
you're a really good dancer.
I know.
You know who's not?
Him.
[increases volume]
[Penny] Happy, what was that?
Are you okay?
[Arthur] Mom, what?
[Penny] That noise!
Did you hear that noise?
I'm watching
an old war movie!
[Penny] Turn it down!
- Um...
- [men continue singing]
Sorry, Mom.
[children chattering]
[indistinct conversation]
You good?
[car horn honks]
[audience laughing]
It's nice to see these
couples out at my show.
I have a wife.
We love to role-play.
- [audience] Ooh!
- Yes, yes, very sexy.
My favorite one
right now is
professor and senior
who really needs
to pass my class
to graduate.
[audience laughing]
- Yes.
- [audience whooping]
So, I'll tell you
how I operate.
I'm a professor at
a prestigious
New England university...
[Arthur laughing]
...and my wife is a senior
in my "Intro To Western Civ."
[audience laughing]
I know. I know.
Why is she a senior in the intro?
I didn't buy it either.
So, she comes to me
during my office hours.
[Arthur laughing]
It's Monday and Wednesday,
three to five.
She says, "Excuse
me, Professor Lewis."
I can't use my real last
name at this college
'cause they
don't hire Jews.
[audience laughing]
It's something I'll address
once I have tenure,
but for now...
She says, "Excuse
me, Professor Lewis,
I think I might be
in danger of failing
your 'Intro to Western Civ, '
and I just want
you to know
I'm willing to do
anything to pass."
And I said,
"Anything?" And she said... [moans]
[Arthur chuckles]
[doorbell buzzing]
- [Arthur] Oh, hey.
- Hey.
Were you following
me today?
Yeah.
I thought
that was you.
I was hoping you'd come
in and rob the place.
I have a gun.
I could come
by tomorrow.
[chuckles]
You're so funny, Arthur.
Yeah.
You know,
I do stand-up comedy.
You should maybe come
see a show sometime.
I could do that.
Yeah?
Yeah. You'll let me know when?
Yeah.
[man] ♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Wiggle your ears ♪
[chorus]
[all] ♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Wiggle your ears ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ And you really
want to show it ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Wiggle your ears ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Stomp your feet ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Stomp your feet ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ And you really
want to show it ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Stomp your feet ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
- [Arthur yelps]
- ♪ Shout "hurray" ♪
♪ Shout "hurray" ♪
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
♪ Shout "hurray" ♪
- ♪ Shout "hurray" ♪
- [child giggles]
♪ If you're happy
and you know it ♪
- [Arthur giggles]
- ♪ And you really want to... ♪
Hoyt, please,
I love this job.
Arthur, I need
to know why
you brought a gun
into a kids' hospital.
It's a prop.
It's part of my act now.
That's bullshit.
Bullshit.
What kind of clown
carries a fucking gun?
Besides,
Randall told me
you tried to buy a .38
off him last week.
Randall told you that?
You're a fuck-up,
Arthur, and a liar.
- You're fired!
- [hangs up]
[dial tone droning]
[announcer on PA]
Jefferson Street.
Next stop, Ninth Ave.
[man 1] I'm telling you,
she wanted my number.
We should've just stayed.
[man 2] You're dreaming, man.
She wasn't interested at all.
[man 1] Are you nuts?
Did you see how close we were dancing?
She was in love.
She couldn't wait to
get away from you.
Ryan! Ryan, am I crazy?
Tell him what you saw.
[slurring drunkenly] Hey,
you want some French fries?
Hello?
Talking to you.
Hey.
[woman]
No, thank you.
[men laughing]
You sure?
They're real good.
Don't ignore him.
He's being nice to you.
Whoo...
[men laughing]
[chuckles]
[laughing continues]
[Arthur laughing]
Is something funny,
asshole?
[gasping]
[continues laughing]
- Bitch!
- [all jeer]
[men snickering]
♪ Isn't it rich? ♪
- ♪ Are we a pair? ♪
- [men laughing]
♪ Me here at last
on the ground ♪
♪ And you
in mid-air ♪
♪ Send in the clowns ♪
[Arthur continues laughing]
♪ Isn't it bliss? ♪
♪ Don't you approve? ♪
♪ One who keeps
tearing around ♪
♪ And one who
can't move ♪
♪ Where are the clowns? ♪
♪ There ought
to be clowns ♪
[both laughing]
So, buddy, tell us,
what's so fucking funny?
Nothing. [laughing]
I have...
I have a condition.
I'll tell you what you
have, you asshole.
[men] Whoa!
[Arthur] Please, stop!
[groans] We got
a kicker, huh?
Hey, hold him steady.
Hold him steady.
Stay down, freak!
[men grunting
and laughing]
[gunshot]
[screaming]
Hey!
[continues screaming]
[breathing heavily]
[man continues screaming]
[announcer on PA]
Ninth Avenue.
Next stop,
Hunter's Point.
Hey!
Stand clear of
the closing doors.
[man yelping]
[groans]
[man whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
[man screams]
[gun clicking]
[panting]
- [ears ringing loudly]
- Shit. Shit.
[panting]
[elevator bell dings]
[man 1] I read it was
a guy in full makeup.
[man 2] No,
it says right here it was a mask.
[man 1] Either way,
I think it's good for business.
They got clowns on the
front of every newspaper.
Big man,
what's the good word?
[Gary] Hey.
["My Name Is Carnival"
playing on radio]
Hey, Arthur,
I heard what happened.
Sorry, mate.
[Randall] Yeah.
It doesn't seem fair,
getting fired like that.
Did you really
bring a gun
to the children's
hospital, Artie?
What the fuck would
you do that for?
Is that part of
your new act, Arthur?
If your dancing
doesn't do the trick,
you're just gonna
shoot yourself?
[men laughing]
Why don't you ask
Randall about it?
It was his gun.
- [Randall] What?
- I still owe you for that,
don't I?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Stop talking
out of your ass, Art.
[honking horn]
[Arthur gasps] Oh, no!
I forgot
to punch out.
[laughing]
["My Name Is Carnival"
continues playing]
[Chuck on TV] And as our city
tries to make sense
of the brutal triple murder
on the subway last week,
we're joined
by Thomas Wayne.
Happy, look,
Thomas Wayne's on TV.
Yes, Mother.
[Thomas] Thanks for
having me on, Chuck.
[Penny] They're asking him about
those horrible
subway murders.
[Chuck] Thank you, Thomas.
I know
this is a difficult time
for you.
Why him?
Looks like
he's gained weight.
[Thomas] Yes,
all three worked for Wayne Investments.
Good, decent, educated.
Although I didn't know
any of them personally.
Like all Wayne employees,
past and present,
they're family.
Did you hear that?
I told you, we're family.
- [shushing]
- [Chuck] There now seems to be
a groundswell of anti-rich
sentiment in the city.
It's almost as if our
less fortunate residents
are taking the side
of the killer.
[Thomas] Yes,
and it's a shame.
It's one
of the reasons why
I'm considering
a run for mayor.
Gotham's lost its way.
What about
the eyewitness report
of the suspect being
a man in a clown mask?
[Thomas] Well,
it makes total sense to me.
What kind of coward would do
something that cold-blooded?
Someone who hides
behind a mask.
Someone who is envious
of those more fortunate
than themselves,
yet they're too scared
to show their own face.
And until those kind of
people change for the better,
those of us who have made
something of our lives
will always look
at those who haven't
as nothing but clowns.
[laughs]
Thomas Wayne,
thank you for coming in this morning.
It's not funny.
[laughs]
I heard this song on
the radio the other day,
and the guy was singing
that his name was Carnival.
[social worker] Arthur...
Which is crazy,
because that's
my clown name at work.
And until
a little while ago,
it was like
nobody ever saw me.
Even I didn't know
if I really existed.
Arthur, I have
some bad news for you.
You don't listen,
do you?
I don't think you
ever really hear me.
You just ask the same
questions every week.
"How's your job?
Are you having any negative thoughts?"
All I have are
negative thoughts,
but you don't
listen anyway.
I said,
for my whole life,
I didn't know
if I even really existed.
But I do.
And people are
starting to notice.
They've cut our funding.
We're closing down
our offices next week.
The city has cut funding
across the board.
Social Services is
part of that.
This is the last time
we'll be meeting.
Okay.
They don't give a shit about
people like you, Arthur.
And they really
don't give a shit
about people
like me, either.
Fuck.
How am I supposed to
get my medication now?
Who do I talk to?
I'm sorry, Arthur.
I think... I think most women
look at sex like buying a car.
You know, like,
"Can I see myself in this long-term?"
"Is it safe?"
"Is it reliable?"
- "Could it kill me?"
- [audience laughing]
Most guys,
we look at sex like parking a car.
We're like,
"There's a spot."
"There's another spot.
- That would work."
- [Arthur exhales deeply]
"Oh, I have to pay?
Never mind."
[audience laughing]
"Handicapped?
I hope no one sees this."
[audience laughing]
All right, that's my time.
Thank you very much, guys.
[audience applauding]
[emcee] One more time
for Sam Morril, y'all.
All right, now,
this next comic describes
himself as
a lifelong Gotham resident
who from a young age
was always told
that his purpose in life
was to bring laughter and joy
into this cold, dark world.
- Um... Okay.
- [audience laughing]
Please help me welcome Arthur
Fleck, y'all.
Arthur Fleck.
[audience applauding]
[sighs nervously]
[laughing]
[snorts]
Hello, it's good to be here.
[laughing]
[clears throat]
[coughing]
[laughing]
[gagging]
I hated school
when I was a kid.
- [microphone feedback]
- [laughing]
[gagging]
[burps]
[breathing heavily]
I hated school as a kid.
[laughing]
My mother
would say,
[imitates Penny]
"You should enjoy it.
One day,
you'll have to work for a living."
[normal voice]
"No, I won't, Ma,
I'm gonna
be a comedian."
[laughing]
Um...
Here's one.
You know,
I was just thinking the other day,
- why are the rich people...
- ["Smile" playing]
[audience laughing]
[audience applauding]
[indistinct chattering]
You believe that shit?
Fuck 'em.
I think the guy that
did it is a hero.
Three less pricks
in Gotham City,
only a million
more to go.
["Smile" continues playing]
[laughing]
[TV playing]
[Murray on TV] And,
buddy, as always,
thanks for the laughs.
I'm sure
we'll see you again.
You know
we'll be here, right?
- I hope.
- [audience laughing]
Tomorrow night, we have Diana
Hudson, Greg Gordon,
and animal expert,
Hugh Little.
Thanks for watching.
Good night,
and always remember,
- that's life.
- ["That's Life" playing]
[audience applauding]
[softly] That's life.
Momma,
time to wake up and go to bed.
- Hmm? Oh...
- [grunting]
Oh, Happy.
Happy, I wrote
a new letter.
Come on,
dance with me.
[Penny] For Thomas Wayne.
It's important.
[Arthur whistles]
[Penny chuckles]
[Arthur humming]
You smell like cologne.
It's 'cause I just
had a big date.
[chuckles] Oh.
Just don't forget
to mail it.
[music continues playing]
[announcer] The Murray
Franklin Show is taped live
before a studio audience
in beautiful downtown
Gotham City.
[music ends]
You're gonna kill me.
You're gonna give me a heart attack!
Don't give me your...
- [pounding on door]
- [Penny] No. No.
I'm not talking to you
until you stop being angry!
Okay.
I'm not angry, Mom.
I'm not angry.
Please.
Mom, is this real?
He's an extraordinary
man, Happy.
He's a very
powerful man.
We were in love.
He said it was best
that we not be together
because of appearances.
And I could never
tell anyone because...
Well, I signed
some papers.
And besides,
you can imagine
what people would say
about Thomas and me.
What they'd say
about you.
What would
they say, Mom?
[Penny crying]
[train horn blowing]
[humming]
[Arthur continues humming]
[Arthur] Hmm.
[Arthur exhales deeply]
Hmm.
[Arthur laughing]
[whistles]
[Arthur singing]
Hi.
What's your name?
I'm Bruce.
Bruce.
I'm Arthur.
That's better.
[Alfred] Bruce! Bruce!
Get away
from that man.
It's okay.
I'm a good guy.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I'm here to see
Mr. Wayne.
Well, you shouldn't be
speaking to his son.
Why did you give him
these flowers?
[Arthur] No,
they're not real.
It's magic.
I was just trying to
make him smile.
Well, it's not funny,
is it?
Do I need
to call the police?
[Arthur] No. Please.
My mother's name is Penny.
Penny Fleck.
She used to work here years ago.
Can you please tell Mr. Wayne
I need to see him?
You are her son.
[Arthur] Yeah.
Did you know her?
[whispers] I know
about the two of them.
She told me everything.
[whispers] There's
nothing to know.
There is no "them."
Your mother
was delusional.
She was
a sick woman.
Don't say that.
Just go.
Mmm?
Before you make a
fool of yourself.
Thomas Wayne
is my father.
[Alfred laughing]
[Alfred yelping]
He left me.
[Alfred choking]
- Let go! Let go!
- [Arthur grunts]
[Alfred continues choking]
[panting]
Keep the respirations
above 15.
Slow and steady.
We got some stairs coming up.
Mom?
What happened?
- Who are you?
- I'm her son.
- What happened?
- You can probably help us
out inside.
We don't know what happened yet.
- Hop in the back of the ambulance.
- [paramedic 2] Step.
[paramedic 1] One more.
We got one more lift.
[paramedic 2] I'm getting
a little resistance here,
Michael.
[paramedics chattering
indistinctly]
[paramedic 1] Lift.
[Arthur] I'm right here.
Excuse me, sir.
Does your mother take
any medications?
- No.
- Excuse me,
- I couldn't hear you.
- No.
Sir, when was the last
time you spoke to her?
I don't know.
[siren wailing]
[Garrity] Mr. Fleck.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm Detective Garrity.
This is my partner,
Detective Burke.
We had a few questions for
you, but you weren't home,
so we spoke
with your mother.
Oh.
What did you
say to her?
Did you do this?
What? No.
No, no, no.
We just asked her some questions,
and she got hysterical.
Hyperventilating,
collapsed and hit
her head pretty hard.
Yeah. The doctor said
she had a stroke.
We're sorry to
hear about that.
But, like I said,
I still have some questions for you.
They're about
the subway killings
that happened
last week.
You've heard about them, right?
Yeah.
It's horrible.
Right.
So, we spoke with your
boss over at Haha's.
He said you were fired
for bringing a gun
into the children's hospital.
- Is that true, Mr. Fleck?
- It was a prop.
It's part
of my act.
I'm a party clown.
All right.
So, why were you fired?
[sighs heavily]
They said
I wasn't funny enough.
Can you imagine that?
If you don't mind,
I have to go take care of my mother.
[Burke] Your boss also
gave us one of your cards.
This condition of yours,
the laughing,
is it real,
or some sort
of clown thing?
- A clown thing?
- Yeah.
I mean, is it part of your act?
What do you think?
[Burke] It's exit only.
She's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna
get a coffee.
You want one?
Yeah.
[audience laughing on TV]
[Murray] So, the other night,
I told my youngest son Billy,
you know, the new one,
the not-so-bright one.
I told him,
"The garbage strike
is still going on, Billy."
And he says, and I'm not
kidding, Billy says,
"So, where are we gonna
get all our garbage from?"
- [laughs]
- [audience laughing]
[audience applauding]
And finally,
in a world where everyone
thinks they could
do my job,
we got this video tape
from Pogo's Comedy Club,
right here in Gotham.
Here's a guy who thinks
if you just keep laughing,
it'll somehow
make you funny.
Check out
this joker.
[laughing]
Oh, my God.
[Arthur on TV] I
hated school as a kid.
But my mother
would always say,
[imitates Penny]
"You should enjoy it.
One day,
you'll have to work for a living."
[normal voice]
"No, I won't, Ma.
I'm gonna be
a comedian."
- [laughing]
- [Arthur laughing on TV]
[laughs] You shoulda
listened to your mother.
[audience laughing
and applauding]
Hey, one more.
One more, Bobby.
All right, let's see one more.
I love this guy.
[Arthur] It's funny,
when I was
a little boy
and told people I was
gonna be a comedian,
everyone laughed at me.
Well, no one's
laughing now.
[audience laughing]
You can say
that again, pal.
[audience applauding]
All right,
we got a great show for you tonight.
Chuck Conby is here,
actress Joanne Mulligan,
and new music from
Mel Rubin and the Stiffs.
[news anchor] As tensions
mount around the metro area,
Mayor Stokes has pleaded
for cooler heads to prevail.
City services
have been affected,
and some businesses
have decided
to remain closed
amid the unrest.
Chuck Stevens
filed this report.
[Chuck] The anger and resentment
that's been building
in the city for weeks
seems close to exploding.
Protesters,
many dressed as clowns,
took to the streets today
in one of several
planned demonstrations
taking on
the city's elite,
including a massive rally
outside
tomorrow night's
benefit at Wayne Hall.
[reporter 1] What's
the point of all this?
[bleep] the rich.
[bleep] Thomas Wayne.
That's what this whole [bleep]
thing is about.
[bleep] the whole system.
[Chuck] Wayne,
who recently announced
he is running for mayor,
will be attending
the benefit.
You might remember
it was Thomas Wayne
who first referred to
many of Gotham's residents
as "clowns."
Today, he offered little
in the way of an apology.
Well, what
I will say is,
there's something wrong
with those people.
I am here
to help them.
I'm gonna
lift them out of poverty,
help make
their lives better.
That is why
I'm running.
And they may not realize
it, but I'm their only hope.
[protesters shouting]
[protesters] Down with Wayne!
Down with Wayne!
[shouting continues]
[lively music
playing in cinema]
- [indistinct chattering]
- [audience laughing]
[audience continues laughing]
- [music continues]
- [audience laughing]
[laughing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Can I help you, pal?
I don't know
what to say.
[flushing]
[Thomas chuckles]
Do you want an
autograph or something?
No.
My name is Arthur.
Penny Fleck
is my mother.
Jesus.
You're the guy that came
to my house yesterday.
- Yes.
- [Thomas laughs]
I'm sorry
I just showed up.
But my mother
told me everything,
and I had
to talk to you.
Look, pal,
I'm not your father.
[chuckling]
What's wrong with you?
Look at us.
I think you are.
Well, that's impossible
because you're adopted,
and I never slept with
your mother.
- I wasn't adopted.
- What do you want from me?
- Money?
- No, I don't...
I wasn't adopted.
Jesus.
She never told you?
Told me what?
[sighs]
Your mother adopted you
while she was working for us.
That's not true.
Why are you
saying that?
Then she was arrested
and committed
to Arkham State Hospital,
when you were
just a little boy.
Why are you
saying this?
I don't need you to
tell me lies.
I know
it seems strange.
I don't mean to
make you uncomfortable.
I don't know why
everyone is so rude.
I don't know
why you are.
I don't want
anything from you.
Maybe a little bit of
warmth, maybe a hug, Dad!
How about just a little
bit of fucking decency?
What is it
with you people?
You say that stuff
about my mother.
She's crazy.
She's... [laughing]
You think
this is funny?
Dad, it's me.
Come on.
[groans]
[Thomas] Touch
my son again,
- I'll fucking kill you.
- [laughing]
[door closes]
[phone ringing]
[Arthur laughing softly]
[answering machine beeps]
Hello, Mr. Fleck.
This is Detective Garrity.
We met the other night
at Gotham General.
My partner and I had a few
more questions for you.
We stopped by your apartment
today, but you weren't home.
Please give me a call
when you get this message.
Again, Detective Garrity,
and my number
is 212... 99.
[answering machine beeps]
[phone ringing]
[Shirley] This message is
for Arthur Fleck.
My name
is Shirley Woods.
I work on
The Murray Franklin Show.
I don't know
if you're aware,
but Murray played
a clip of your stand-up
on the show recently,
and we have gotten an amazing
response from our viewers.
Murray asked me to give you
a call and see if you're...
Who is this?
Oh, hi,
this is Shirley Woods.
I'm the show booker from
Live with Murray Franklin.
Is this Arthur?
Yes.
Hi, Arthur.
Well, as I was saying,
we've gotten a lot of
calls about your clip.
Amazing responses.
And Murray asked if I
would reach out to you
to see if you would
come on as his guest.
Murray wants me
on The Murray Franklin Show?
Yeah.
Isn't that great?
He'd love to talk to you,
maybe do some of your act?
That sound good
to you?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Can we set up a date right now?
Are you available
next Thursday?
[inaudible]
[indistinct announcement
on PA]
[clerk] Hey.
[sighs] Man,
I'm sorry about that, my man.
All records 10 years or older,
they store in the basement,
and you're talking about
something 30 years ago, so...
Can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
How does someone
wind up in here?
Have they all,
all the people committed crimes?
Well, yeah, some have.
You know,
some are just crazy.
Pose dangers to
themselves and others.
Some just got
nowhere else to go.
Don't know what to do, you know?
- Yeah. I hear you, brother.
- Hmm.
Sometimes,
I don't know what to do.
Last time, I ended up taking
it out on some people.
I thought it was gonna bother
me, but it really hasn't.
What's that?
I fucked up and
did some bad shit.
[chuckles]
You know
what I'm talking about,
it's so hard to just try
and be happy all the time.
Hey, listen, man.
I'm just
an administrative assistant.
Like a clerk,
you know.
All I do
is file paperwork.
I don't know
what to tell you.
But you should
see somebody.
You know,
they got programs,
city services,
stuff like that.
Oh, yeah.
[in high-pitched voice]
They cut all those.
[clerk laughs]
All right, here it is. Fleck.
Penny Fleck.
Let's see.
Diagnosed by
Dr. Benjamin Stoner.
Oh. "The patient suffers
from delusional psychosis
and narcissistic
personality disorder." Mmm.
"Was found guilty
of endangering
the welfare
of her own child."
What?
You said
she's your mother.
Uh...
I'm sorry, man. Like I said,
I can't release these records,
you know,
without proper forms.
I could
get in trouble.
Look, if you want to bring
your mom in here to sign,
that'll be much easier,
but I can't let this go
without her signature, okay?
I'm sorry.
No, man! Shit!
Come on, man.
Give it...
Hey! Hey!
[panting]
[door closes]
[Stoner] We went over this, Penny.
You adopted him.
We have all the
paperwork right here.
[Young Penny]
That's not true.
Thomas had that
all made up,
so it stayed
our secret.
[gasps]
[Stoner] You also
stood by
while one
of your boyfriends
repeatedly abused
your adopted son
and battered you.
[laughing]
Penny,
your son was found
tied to a radiator
in your filthy apartment.
Malnourished with multiple
bruises across his body
and severe trauma
to his head.
[Arthur laughing]
[Young Penny] I
never heard him cry.
He's always been such
a happy little boy.
[laughing tearfully]
[crying]
[elevator bell dings]
- [GiGi whines]
- [Sophie shushing]
[Sophie] It's time
for bed.
[door closes]
[gasps] Oh, my God!
- What are you doing in here?
- [thunder rumbling]
You're in the
wrong apartment.
Your name's Arthur, right?
You live
down the hall.
I really
need you to leave.
My little girl is sleeping
in the other room.
Please.
I had a bad day.
Can I call someone?
Is your mother home?
[gasps]
[chuckling]
[door closes]
[laughing]
[sniffling]
[sirens wailing]
[continues laughing]
- [banging on wall]
- [man] Shut up!
[continues laughing]
[heart monitor beeping]
Hey, Penny.
Penny Fleck.
I always hated
that name.
You know how you used to tell me
that my laugh
was a condition?
That there was
something wrong with me?
There isn't.
That's the real me.
[Penny, weakly] Happy.
Happy. Hmm.
I haven't been happy
one minute of
my entire fucking life.
You know
what's funny?
You know what really
makes me laugh?
I used to think that my
life was a tragedy...
[grunts]
...but now I realize
it's a fucking comedy.
[muffled grunting]
[heart monitor
beeping rapidly]
[Penny fighting]
[muffled screaming]
[heart monitor
stops beeping]
[exhales]
- [music playing]
- [audience applauding]
[fast-forwarding]
- [music playing]
- [audience applauding]
[fast-forwarding]
[Murray] A very fine actor.
He's got a new movie
called American Playboy
opening this week
across the country.
Will you please
welcome a good friend
of the show,
Mr. Ethan Chase.
- [music playing]
- [audience applauding]
Good to see you, Ethan.
You're looking great, Ethan.
[Ethan] Thank you very much.
You're looking good yourself.
[Murray] Ah,
can't complain.
Hey, Murray.
Thanks so much for having...
Thank you so much for
having me on the show.
It's been a lifelong
dream of mine.
[Murray] I'm nervous
right now.
[audience laughing on video]
- [Ethan] You are?
- [Murray] I am nervous.
Hey, Murray.
I've been on...
[muttering]
[sighs]
[continues muttering]
I'm sorry.
What's that?
Oh, that's
very funny, Murray.
You know,
I'm also a comedian.
Would you like
to hear a joke?
[audience cheering]
Yeah?
All of you?
Okay.
Knock...
Knock, knock.
[audience gasps]
- [chuckles]
- [audience laughing]
Knock, knock.
[gun clicks]
- [audience laughing]
- [gun clatters]
[audience applauding]
["That's Life" playing]
- [doorbell buzzing]
- [music continues playing]
[doorbell buzzing insistently]
Coming.
[Gary] Hey, Arthur.
How's it going?
Oh, hey, guys.
Come on in.
Did you get
a new gig?
No.
Oh, you must be going down
to that rally at City Hall.
I hear
it's gonna be nuts.
Oh, is that today?
Yeah.
What's with
the makeup then?
My mom died.
I'm celebrating.
Right. We heard.
That's why
we came by.
We figured, you know,
you could use some cheering up.
[Arthur] Aw, that's sweet.
But, no, I feel good.
Yeah, I stopped
taking my medication.
I feel
a lot better now.
Oh, okay.
Good for you.
So, hey, listen,
I don't know if you heard,
but the cops have been
coming around the shop,
talking to all the guys
about those subway murders.
- And, um...
- They didn't talk to me.
That's because the suspect
was a regular-sized person.
If it was a fucking midget,
you'd be in jail right now.
[Arthur laughing]
Anyway, um,
Hoyt said that
they talked to you,
and now
they're looking for me,
and I just wanna know
what you said.
Make sure
our stories line up.
- Seeing as how you're my boy.
- Yeah, that's important.
- That makes a lot of sense.
- You know what I mean?
Thank you, Randall.
Thank you so much.
- [Randall groaning]
- [Gary screaming]
[Gary] Arthur!
- No!
- [Randall's head thudding]
What?
No!
- [Arthur panting]
- [Gary sobbing]
Why would
you do that, Arthur?
- [breathing rapidly]
- [Gary continues sobbing]
Do you watch
The Murray Franklin Show?
- [Gary whimpering]
- Yeah.
I'm gonna be
on tonight.
[whimpering]
[in cockney accent]
It fucking crazy, innit?
Me on the telly.
What the fuck, Arthur?
[normal voice] What?
It's okay, Gary.
You can go.
[Gary groaning]
I'm not gonna
hurt you.
Oh!
Don't look.
Just go.
[Arthur yells]
[whimpering]
[crying] Fuck.
[sighs tearfully]
Hey, Arthur?
Yeah?
[stammering] Arthur,
can you get the lock?
Shit.
Sorry, Gary.
Gary?
Yeah.
You were the only one
that was ever nice to me.
Skedaddle.
[exhales]
[rock music playing]
[elevator bell dings]
[sinister music playing]
Hey, Arthur!
We need to talk.
[Arthur] Oh!
Hey! Stop, Arthur!
[Garrity] Arthur!
Watch it!
Out of the way!
[Burke] Move!
- [horns honking]
- Arthur!
Shit.
[detectives] Hey! Hey!
[Garrity] Arthur, stop!
[Burke] Go! Go!
[announcer on PA] Now
departing, O-Train, downtown.
Stand clear of
the closing doors.
[panting]
Hold that train!
Hold it!
Get out!
Get outta here!
[announcer on PA]
Next stop, Bedford Park.
[crowd yelling]
Masks off!
Get your mask off!
Signs down! Now!
Police! Signs down!
Signs down.
What the fuck!
[both grunting]
- [man] Beat his ass!
- [crowd shouting]
Stop fighting! Police!
Police! Get down!
Get down!
Get the fuck back!
Police! Get down.
Get the fuck down!
Stay the fuck back!
Down!
[gunshot]
[groans]
What the...
Arthur!
Burke!
- [Arthur laughing]
- [crowd shouting]
Don't do it!
[laughs]
Two officers on the train
were violently confronted
by the crowd,
and tonight are in serious
but stable condition
at Gotham Metropolitan.
- [laughs]
- We're going live now to
co-anchor Courtney Weathers,
who's standing by outside
the Bedford Park Station,
near where the shooting
took place.
Courtney,
what's the scene there?
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
Murray.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's Mr. Franklin, buddy.
Oh, come on, Gene.
That's all bullshit.
Thank you, Murray.
I feel like
I know you.
I've been
watching you forever.
Thank you.
What's with the face?
I mean,
are you part of the protest?
No.
No, I don't believe
in any of that.
I don't believe
in anything.
I just thought it'd
be good for my act.
For your act?
Didn't you hear
what happened on the subway?
Some clown got killed.
He's aware of that.
He's aware of that. Yeah.
No, I hadn't heard.
- Yeah.
- You see? This is
what I'm telling you.
The audience is
gonna go crazy
if you put this guy on.
Maybe for a bit,
but not a whole segment.
Gene, it's gonna work.
It's gonna work.
- We're gonna go with it.
- [Arthur and Murray laugh]
Thank you, Murray.
Couple rules, though.
No cursing.
No off-color material.
We do a clean show.
- Okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
You'll go on
right after Dr. Sally.
I love Dr. Sally.
Good, good.
Someone will
- come and get you, okay?
- Okay. Perfect.
Good luck.
- Thanks, Murray.
- Okay.
- Murray, one small thing.
- Yeah.
When you
bring me out,
can you
introduce me as Joker?
What's wrong
with your real name?
That's what you
called me on the show.
A joker.
Do you remember?
- Did I?
- [Gene] I don't know.
Well, if you say so, kid,
you know, Joker it is.
It's good.
Thanks, Murray.
[gun clicks]
[Murray] I'll try it,
you know,
but I'm not sure my
wife will let me do it.
[audience laughing]
Maybe my next wife.
- [Murray laughing]
- [audience cheering]
You gotta see our next
guest for yourself.
I'm pretty sure this
guy could use a doctor.
- [audience laughing]
- [Dr. Sally] Oh!
Does he have
sexual problems?
[Murray] Oh, he looks like
he's got a lot of problems.
[audience laughing]
All right, Bobby,
let's show that clip one last time.
[Arthur laughing
on video]
[Arthur] I hated
school as a kid.
But my mother
would always say,
[imitates Penny]
"You should enjoy it.
One day,
you'll have to work for a living."
[normal voice]
"No, I won't, Ma.
I'm gonna be
a comedian."
[Arthur laughing on video]
- [Murray] Okay. You may...
- [audience laughing]
You may have seen that
clip of our next guest.
Now, before he comes
out, I just want to say
that we're
all heartbroken
about what's going on
in the city tonight.
But this is how he
wanted to come out,
and honestly,
I think we could all use a good laugh.
So, please welcome, Joker.
- [music playing]
- [audience applauding]
[audience cheering]
[audience whooping
and whistling]
Are you
all right, Doctor?
[audience laughing]
Well,
that was quite an entrance.
[scattered laughter
from audience]
You okay?
Yeah.
This is exactly
how I imagined it.
Well, that makes
one of us.
[audience laughing]
[audience applauding]
So, can you tell us
about this look?
When we spoke earlier,
you mentioned that this look
is not a political statement.
Is that right?
That's right, Murray.
I'm not political.
I'm just trying to
make people laugh.
- And how's that going for you?
- [audience laughing]
[laughing]
So, I know
you're a comedian.
You been working on
any new material?
You wanna
tell us a joke?
[audience applauding]
Yeah?
Okay.
[audience laughing]
He's got a book.
A book of jokes.
Take your time.
We got all night.
[audience laughing]
[Murray chuckles]
Okay, okay.
Here's one.
Knock, knock.
And you had to
look that up?
- [laughing]
- [audience laughing]
[audience applauding]
I want to
get it right.
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
It's the police, ma'am.
Your son's been hit
by a drunk driver.
- He's dead. [laughing]
- [audience gasps]
[plays sad note]
- [audience booing]
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, you cannot
joke about that.
Yeah, that's
not funny, Arthur.
That's not that kind of
humor we do on this show.
Okay. I'm...
Yeah, I'm sorry.
It's just, you know,
it's been a rough few weeks, Murray.
[chuckling]
Ever since
I killed those three
Wall Street guys.
[all gasp]
Okay, I'm waiting
for the punch line.
There is
no punch line.
- It's not a joke.
- [audience murmuring]
You're serious,
aren't you?
You're telling us
you killed
those three young men
on the subway?
[Arthur] Mmm-hmm.
And why should
we believe you?
I got nothing
left to lose.
Nothing can
hurt me anymore.
[laughs]
My life is
nothing but a comedy.
[audience booing]
Well, let me
get this straight,
you think that killing
those guys is funny?
I do.
And I'm tired of
pretending it's not.
Comedy is subjective,
Murray.
Isn't that
what they say?
All of you,
the system
that knows so much,
you decide
what's right or wrong.
The same way that you
decide what's funny or not!
[man] Get him off!
Well, okay,
I think I might understand
that you did this to
start a movement,
to become a symbol?
Come on, Murray.
Do I look like
the kind of clown
that could
start a movement?
I killed those guys
because they were awful.
Everybody is awful
these days.
It's enough to
make anyone crazy.
[Murray] Okay.
So, that's it, you're crazy.
That's your defense for
killing three young men?
No.
They couldn't carry a
tune to save their lives.
[audience booing]
Oh, why is everybody so
upset about these guys?
If it was me
dying on the sidewalk,
you'd walk
right over me!
I pass you every day,
and you don't notice me.
But these guys, what,
because Thomas Wayne
went and cried about them on TV?
You have a problem
with Thomas Wayne, too?
Yes, I do.
Have you seen what it's
like out there, Murray?
Do you ever actually
leave the studio?
Everybody just yells and
screams at each other.
Nobody's civil anymore.
Nobody thinks what it's
like to be the other guy.
You think men like
Thomas Wayne ever think
what it's like to be
someone like me?
To be somebody but themselves?
They don't.
They think that
we'll just sit there
and take it,
like good little boys!
That we won't werewolf
and go wild!
You finished?
I mean, it's so much
self-pity, Arthur.
You sound like
you're making excuses
for killing
those young men.
Not everybody,
and I'll tell you this,
not everyone is awful.
You're awful, Murray.
Me? I'm awful?
Oh, yeah,
how am I awful?
Playing my video.
Inviting me
on this show.
You just wanted to
make fun of me.
You're just like
the rest of them.
You don't know the first
thing about me, pal.
Look what happened,
because of what you did. What it led to.
There are riots
out there.
Two policemen are
in critical condition,
- and you're laughing.
- [laughs]
You're laughing.
Someone was killed today,
because of what you did.
I know.
How about another joke, Murray?
No, I think we've had
enough of your jokes.
- What do you get...
- I don't think so.
...when you cross
a mentally-ill loner
with a society
that abandons him
and treats him
like trash?
Call the police, Gene!
- I'll tell you what you get!
- Call the police.
You get what you
fucking deserve!
[audience screaming]
[laughing]
- [screaming continues]
- [gun clatters]
Good night.
And always remember, that's...
[upbeat music playing]
[news anchor 1]
Breaking news.
Popular TV talk show host,
Murray Franklin
was shot dead tonight on the
live telecast of his program.
The man who was
introduced by Franklin
as "Joker" is
currently under arrest.
Police led the suspect
handcuffed out of the studio.
- [Arthur shouting]
- [overlapping chatter]
...merely just a punch
line to a joke...
[Arthur] You get what
you [bleep] deserve!
[reporter 1]
Looting and rioting
have intensified here...
[reporter 2] ...rioting
throughout the city.
[Arthur] ...with a society
that abandons him
and treats him
like trash?
[news anchor 2]
This mob of clowns...
[reporter 1] ...many
wearing clown masks.
[overlapping chatter
continues]
[Arthur] If it was me
dying on the sidewalk,
- you'd walk right over me.
- [news anchor 2] To all of
those who have been
ignored by the system.
[Arthur] And always remember,
that's life!
[reporter 3] And as you see,
Gotham is burning.
[music playing]
[sirens wailing]
[looters shouting]
[dispatcher chattering
on radio]
[shouting continues]
[store alarms ringing]
[laughing]
[officer 1] Stop laughing, you freak!
This isn't funny.
[officer 2] Yeah,
the whole fucking city's on fire
'cause of
what you did.
[dispatcher] All units,
fire reported, north of alley.
Code Four
for medical.
I know.
Isn't it beautiful?
[chuckles]
[looters shouting]
[shouting continues]
[sirens wailing]
Go over there.
Hey, Wayne.
You get what you
fucking deserve.
No! Pal!
[Mrs. Wayne screaming]
[gunshot]
[body thuds]
[looters shouting]
[coughing]
[man] Come on,
get up!
Come on,
man, get up.
[crowd shouting and cheering]
[crowd continues
shouting and cheering]
[Arthur laughing]
[continues laughing]
What's so funny?
Just thinking
of a joke.
[Arthur continues laughing]
Do you want
to tell it to me?
You wouldn't get it.
["That's Life" playing]
[Arthur] ♪ That's life ♪
♪ And as funny
as it may seem ♪
♪ Some people
get their kicks ♪
♪ Stompin' on a dream ♪
♪ But I don't let it,
let it get me down ♪
♪ 'Cause this
fine old world ♪
["That's Life"
continues playing]